misterenglish.com 2007-10-14

# Privacy Policy

MISTER ENGLISH PRIVACY POLICY

* * *

Welcome to MisterEnglish (the "Site").

Short Version:

We will never sell, trade, or otherwise release your name & email address to any outside party. Period. We respect your privacy. Any purchases made on this site are processed safely through famous 3rd party providers such as 2checkout.com or PayPal.com. Credit Card information never passes through nor is your credit card number ever stored in any way on our servers.

プライバシー問題に関して。 学校情報及び生徒個人情報を含むあなたのアカウント全ては厳重に保護、守秘されています。いかなる理由をもってもあなたのアカウントにあるデータ流出、データ共有、データ売買をすることはありません。 

Long Version:

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. 

This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by MisterEnglish (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").

"Personally Identifiable Information" 

refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

What Personally Identifiable Information is collected? 

We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.

What organizations are collecting the information? 

In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such services as credit, may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers (e.g. when buying a Database from MisterEnglish payment is made through PayPal.com or 2Checkout.com - since MisterEnglish does NOT see nor store credit card numbers). We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?

We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. For telephone support, we require MisterEnglish Authorized Customers to authenticate their identity with a PIN number to protect their privacy.

With whom may the information may be shared?

Personally Identifiable Information is not shared intentially without permission from the Authorized Customer. We may share aggregated information such as the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.

How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?

Personally Identifiable Information collected by MisterEnglish is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of MisterEnglish except for use as indicated above. 

What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?

Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at [mail(at)MisterEnglish(dot)com](mailto:mail@MisterEnglish.com)

Are Cookies Used on the Site?

Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 20 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.

How does MisterEnglish use login information?

MisterEnglish uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?

3rd Party payment processing companies such as PayPal and 2checkout.com in so far as they need to process a payment purchased on the Site. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.

How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?

All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers are processed through 3rd party providers such as PayPal or 2checkout.com, and therefore are NOT stored on MisterEnglish servers. Customer information such as passwords are protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.

How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?

Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at [mail(at)MisterEnglish(dot)com](mailto:mail@MisterEnglish.com)

Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?

We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting [mail(at)MisterEnglish(dot)com](mailto:mail@MisterEnglish.com). However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward. 

What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?

We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. 

Links:

This web site may contain links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours. 

(c) 2007 MisterEnglish , All rights reserved.  
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Site is expressly prohibited.
